[
  {
    "id": 1000,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "can i get head massage",
    "answer": "Yes, head massage is available at Glow & Go Salon.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T11:13:33.011Z",
    "status": "undelivered"
  },
  {
    "id": 1001,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "can i get head massage",
    "answer": "Yes, head massage is available at Glow & Go Salon.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T11:22:45.277Z",
    "status": "undelivered"
  },
  {
    "id": 1002,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "can i get head massage",
    "answer": "Yes, head massage is available.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T11:38:13.902Z",
    "status": "undelivered"
  },
  {
    "id": 1003,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "can i get head massage",
    "answer": "Yes, head massage is available at Glow & Go Salon.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T11:40:51.667Z",
    "status": "undelivered"
  },
  {
    "id": 1004,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "can i get head massage",
    "answer": "Yes, head massage is available at Glow & Go Salon.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T11:42:14.839Z",
    "status": "undelivered"
  },
  {
    "id": 1005,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "can i get head massage",
    "answer": "Yes, head massage is available at Glow & Go Salon.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T11:43:20.335Z",
    "status": "undelivered"
  },
  {
    "id": 1006,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you have orange?",
    "answer": "Yes, orange is available.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T11:52:59.918Z",
    "status": "undelivered"
  },
  {
    "id": 1007,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "can i get head massage",
    "answer": "Yes, head massage is available.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T11:57:14.946Z",
    "status": "undelivered"
  },
  {
    "id": 1008,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you have orange?",
    "answer": "Yes, orange is available.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T11:57:32.635Z",
    "status": "undelivered"
  },
  {
    "id": 1009,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you ahve tea?",
    "answer": "No, tea is not available.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T11:57:40.401Z",
    "status": "undelivered"
  },
  {
    "id": 1010,
    "userId": "20193e19-4120-431d-a00f-c334854ea1a8",
    "question": "qwerty",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear. Please feel free to ask again with more specific or relevant information.",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T12:41:30.454Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1011,
    "userId": "20193e19-4120-431d-a00f-c334854ea1a8",
    "question": "qwerty",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear. Please feel free to ask again with more specific or relevant information.",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T12:42:39.545Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1012,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you provide jars?",
    "answer": "Yes, we provide jars.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T12:43:24.635Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1013,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you hav coffee",
    "answer": "Yes, coffee is available at Glow & Go Salon.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T12:46:01.012Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1014,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you hav coffee",
    "answer": "Yes, coffee is available.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T12:46:10.043Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1015,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you hav coffee",
    "answer": "Yes, coffee is available.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T12:46:30.543Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1016,
    "userId": "79cb44b2-34a1-430c-a61b-2b4c02f961ef",
    "question": "qwerty",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear. Please feel free to ask again with more specific or relevant information.",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T13:02:27.567Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "pending"
  },
  {
    "id": 1017,
    "userId": "79cb44b2-34a1-430c-a61b-2b4c02f961ef",
    "question": "do you have mobile?",
    "answer": "Yes, we have mobile available.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T13:03:10.281Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "pending"
  },
  {
    "id": 1018,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you hav coffee",
    "answer": "Yes, coffee is available.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T14:54:17.215Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1019,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you hav coffee",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear. Please feel free to ask again with more specific or relevant information.",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T14:55:48.507Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1020,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you hav coffee",
    "answer": "Yes, coffee is available at Glow & Go Salon.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T14:57:48.037Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1021,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you hav coffee",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear. Please feel free to ask again with more specific or relevant information.",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T14:57:57.301Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1022,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you have chai?",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear. Please feel free to ask again with more specific or relevant information.",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:01:42.475Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1023,
    "userId": "20193e19-4120-431d-a00f-c334854ea1a8",
    "question": "hola",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear. Please feel free to ask again with more specific or relevant information.",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:03:14.125Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1024,
    "userId": "20193e19-4120-431d-a00f-c334854ea1a8",
    "question": "hola",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear. Please feel free to ask again with more specific or relevant information.",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:05:23.960Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1025,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "qweryy",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear. Please feel free to ask again with more specific or relevant information.",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:13:12.352Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1026,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "are you on ig?",
    "answer": "Yes, our Instagram username is setia.lakshay.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:14:31.899Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1027,
    "userId": "20193e19-4120-431d-a00f-c334854ea1a8",
    "question": "hola",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear. Please feel free to ask again with more specific or relevant information.",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:35:39.756Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1028,
    "userId": "20193e19-4120-431d-a00f-c334854ea1a8",
    "question": "facebook",
    "answer": "Sorry, facebook is not available.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:39:53.335Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1029,
    "userId": "20193e19-4120-431d-a00f-c334854ea1a8",
    "question": "facebook",
    "answer": "Sorry, Facebook is not available.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:42:18.048Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1030,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you hav coffee",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear. Please feel free to ask again with more specific or relevant information.",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:42:26.191Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1031,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you hav coffee",
    "answer": "Yes, coffee is available at Glow & Go Salon.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:42:42.046Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1032,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you have chai?",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear. Please feel free to ask again with more specific or relevant information.",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:43:34.728Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1033,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "are you on ig?",
    "answer": "Yes, our Instagram username is setia.lakshay.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:43:43.706Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1034,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you have straightening?",
    "answer": "Yes, we provide straightening services. The price for straightening is $150.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:47:19.219Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1035,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "qwerty",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear. Please feel free to ask again with more specific or relevant information.",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:56:17.933Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1036,
    "userId": "20193e19-4120-431d-a00f-c334854ea1a8",
    "question": "do you provide coffee?",
    "answer": "Yes, coffee is available at Glow & Go Salon.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T21:35:38.534Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1037,
    "userId": "20193e19-4120-431d-a00f-c334854ea1a8",
    "question": "do you provide coffee?",
    "answer": "Yes, coffee is available at Glow & Go Salon.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T21:38:34.784Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1038,
    "userId": "20193e19-4120-431d-a00f-c334854ea1a8",
    "question": "do you provide coffee?",
    "answer": "Yes, coffee is available at Glow & Go Salon.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T21:39:35.407Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1039,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "are you on ig?",
    "answer": "Yes, we are on Instagram! You can find us at cute_n_cuts.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T21:40:36.776Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1040,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you have straightening?",
    "answer": "Yes, we offer straightening services. The price is $150. Would you like to book an appointment? You can call us or book via our website: https://glowandgo.com.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T21:54:20.910Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1041,
    "userId": "20193e19-4120-431d-a00f-c334854ea1a8",
    "question": "dummy request",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T21:58:05.219Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1042,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "qweryy",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T21:59:43.851Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1043,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "qweryy",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T21:59:44.335Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1044,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "are you on ig?",
    "answer": "Yes, our Instagram handle is cute_n_cuts.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:00:14.520Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1045,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "qwerty",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:00:21.842Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1046,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you have straightening?",
    "answer": "Yes, we offer straightening services. The price for straightening is $150.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:03:07.158Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1047,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "demo",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:03:22.738Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1048,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "demo",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:04:24.145Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1049,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "qwerty",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:04:35.235Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1050,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "demo",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:05:47.371Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1051,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "qwe",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:07:32.575Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1052,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "get me a pizza",
    "answer": "I am sorry, pizza is unavailable.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:13:31.969Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1053,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "qweqe",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:15:26.211Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1054,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "qwe",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:17:37.883Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1055,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "qwe",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:19:11.495Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1056,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "qwe",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:20:53.797Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1057,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "qwe",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:24:56.934Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1058,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "qwe",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:26:00.712Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1059,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you have ehatsapp",
    "answer": "Yes, our WhatsApp number is 123456789.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:26:36.705Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1060,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "qwerty",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:38:06.347Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1061,
    "userId": "b58c4b8c-ed54-4162-a547-5815a7752b47",
    "question": "do you have chai?",
    "answer": "Yes, we do have chai available.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T22:49:46.813Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1062,
    "userId": "95b04cd9-1c84-4565-b48b-c53e62af870b",
    "question": "can i call you on whatsapp?",
    "answer": "Yes, you can call us on WhatsApp. Our WhatsApp number is 1234567890.\n",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T23:13:31.370Z",
    "status": "resolved",
    "delivery": "done"
  },
  {
    "id": 1063,
    "userId": "95b04cd9-1c84-4565-b48b-c53e62af870b",
    "question": "qwerty",
    "answer": "Your question was either incomplete or unclear...",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T23:14:09.188Z",
    "status": "rejected",
    "delivery": "done"
  }
]